panic-away.com 2016-11-03

# Panic Away

**PRIVACY POLICY  
(IMPORTANT NOTICE — PLEASE READ)   
This Privacy Policy describes the terms of our commitment to your privacy.**

PERSONS OR PARTIES COVERED  
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover all visitors to this website‚ all subscribers to lists or newsletters whether paid or unpaid‚ all members or affiliates whether paid or unpaid‚ and all customers. Persons who visit or view this website‚ whether intentionally or unintentionally‚ whether solicited or unsolicited‚ are described herein as “Visitors” and are parties to this Privacy Policy. Subscribers to lists or Newsletters are referred to herein as “Subscribers” and are parties to the Privacy Policy. Persons who join an organization or marketing endeavor (e.g. “affiliates”) promoted by this website are called “Members” herein and are covered by this Privacy Policy. Finally‚ anyone who orders‚ attempts to order‚ or receives a product sold (recipients) or advertised on or delivered from this website‚ even at no cost‚ is called a “Customer” herein and is subject to this Privacy Policy not only by passive acceptance‚ but by virtue of the Purchase Agreement contract. The website‚ its agents‚ owners‚ operators‚ and employees are referred to collectively herein as “Website”‚ “Site”‚ and/or “Seller”. 

PERSONS EXCLUDED FROM THIS WEBSITE ARE STILL COVERED  
In the event that a person excluded from this website because of the Terms of Use or from denial of service by the website‚ who nonetheless unlawfully views this site‚ that person remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and is in violation of the Terms of Use.

PERSONS UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE ARE EXCLUDED FROM THIS WEBSITE  
This website is not lawfully accessible to persons under the age of 18 or who are otherwise covered by the provisions of the Child Online Privacy Act of 1998 (COPA). If you are under the age of 18 you must leave this site immediately. Fraudulent use of this website may make you subject to civil or criminal sanctions.

VIEWING AND/OR USE AND/OR COMMUNICATION IS CONSTRUED AS ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY  
Acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy is a portion of the consideration required for your right to visit the website. If you do not accept these terms‚ you have no right to visit this site and you are fraudulently using this site.

A NOTE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS (ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 2003 —OPPA)  
It is the intent of the Privacy Policy to comply with the California Act. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the act. In summary‚ you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. This is not usually personally identifiable. If you purchase a product or service via this website (and thereby become covered by the Act)‚ the purchase agreement you electronically sign prior to purchase allows the website to collect and archive all the personal information you provide and to transmit and/or transfer that personal information to third parties. There is no way you can modify this information and you have no right to do so. Under the terms of the purchase agreement‚ you have no right to view or receive any information about our database. In the event that the website‚ under advice of counsel agrees to divulge information‚ the requesting party must submit whatever information is demanded by the website in insure that the website is releasing information to the correct party. Other provisions of the OPPA may exempt this website from complying. While we take measures to ensure that outside parties do not have access to any information we have about you‚ we do not warranty that outside parties will not breach our system and thus have access to your information. (You should know that merchant service providers do not allow us access to your credit card information.) This Privacy Policy also is subject to change without notice. You are required to read it prior to using the website. By interacting with the website you agree to the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy. By using the website or purchasing a product through this website‚ you waive the right to use state or federal court systems to address complaints and‚ instead‚ agree to use the American Arbitration Association located in a city and county specified herein.

ABOUT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION THIS WEBSITE COLLECTS AND HOW IT IS USED  
This website routinely collects information about its visitors‚ subscribers‚ members‚ and customers. This information is obtained in various ways‚ such as:

VISITOR‚ SUBSCRIBER‚ MEMBER‚ OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM ‘REGISTRATION’  
Registration means that the Visitor‚ Subscriber‚ Member or Customer takes active‚ positive steps to communicate information to this website. This can include pages or ‘pop ups’ where you register for a newsletter or subscribe to a mailing list; it can include your participation in visitor surveys; it can include requesting information from the website via email‚ mail‚ or courier; it may be from joining an affiliate program or other membership organization‚ paid or unpaid; it may be from ordering a product.

Occasionally complete credit card information may be provided to the website via fax or a fill–in form rather than regular secure merchant service processing. This information is kept at the highest level of security and is never divulged to anyone except the merchant service provider or for the purpose of communication with the customer.

ONLINE ORDERING  
Online ordering via SSL encrypted communication provided by shopping cart services supporting merchant service companies like Visa and Master Card provides information to the website but does not provide complete credit card numbers. In the process of online ordering‚ the customer provides‚ name‚ address‚ city‚ state‚ email address‚ phone number‚ CVV2 (back of card) number‚ and‚ occasionally a member password. You should consider all this information available to the website. This information is used to deliver the product‚ but under the Purchase Agreement you also approve its use for general solicitation purposes.

**Please see our payment processor’s Privacy Policy concerning the information collected with the purpose of processing online payments. Our payment processor is ClickBank®. You can read their Privacy Policy[here.](http://www.clickbank.com/privacy.html)**
